-Hey, guys.. -Wait! Let me tell them.
-嘿，伙计们… -等等，我来跟他们讲。
-Sure. -Joey's gonna be..
-好 -乔伊要...
a celebrity guest on a game show.
在一个益智节目中做嘉宾了。
Really? Which one?
真的？哪个节目？
Fish. Seaweed.
鱼，海草
-A sunken ship. -Things you find in the ocean.
-沉船… -海中之物…
-You're gonna be on Pyramid! -Yeah.
-你要上智力金字塔! -对
-That was our favorite game show ever. -Except for Match Game.
-哦，那是我们最喜欢的益智节目了! -除了匹配赛以外!
Or Win, Lose or Draw.
还有输赢签。
What did I marry into?
瞧瞧我结的亲家。
You guys wanna come and watch me tape the show?
你们想明天来看我录节目吗？
Oh, we can't. We're throwing Phoebe a bachelorette party.
不行，我们要给菲比开个婚前告别单身狂欢。
Yeah. Sorry, boys, this ride's closing.
对喽，抱歉，兄弟们，此路不通。
And Chandler and I have this stupid college alumni thing.
哦，钱勒和我要参加一个校友聚会。
I can't believe you get to meet Donny Osmond.
难以置信你要跟多尼・奥斯蒙德做节目。
Seriously?
当真？
Ross and I always wanted to be Donny and Marie.
罗斯和我以前总想学多尼和马瑞一样。
You guys just keep getting cooler and cooler.
你们俩还越说越起劲儿了。
Yeah, we used to perform for our family and friends.
对，我们以前还在家里和朋友面前表演过嘞。
Oh, God, that's right. I blocked that out.
哦，没错，我还真把它给忘了。
I'm leaving you.
我要离开你了。
The One Where The Stripper Cries
rainystar压制iPod-MP4
It's so weird to see all these people again.
又见到这些人了。
Oh, my God, look. There's Jeffrey Klarik.
哦，我的上帝，那是杰佛.克拉瑞。
-Who? -He was roommates with John Rosoff.
-谁? -约翰.卢瑟夫的室友。
He went out with Andrea Tamborino.
他当时跟安卓.特布里诺拍拖。
She dumped him for Michael Skloff.
她后来又跟麦克.斯克劳夫好上了。
Did I go to this school?
我上的是这所学校吗？
Hey, there's Missy Goldberg. You gotta remember her.
嘿，那是米西.戈尔伯格，你肯定记得她。
Sure. Nice.
当然，她很正点。
Dude, you're married to my sister.
哥们儿，你可跟我老妹结了婚的。
You're right. By saying "nice, " I'm virtually licking her.
你说的没错，我夸她正点就是跟她不正经了？
Hey, I hear she's single again. You think I should ask her out?
嘿，我听说她又单身了 你说我是不是该跟她约会呢？
Are you asking permission to break the pact?
你是不是想要打破君子协定？
Yes, please.
对了，求求你。
Hey. Hey, check out the fliers for the band.
瞧瞧乐队的传单。
-I made them on a Macintosh. -Awesome.
-我在机房的苹果机上做的。 -乖乖
The name really stands out.
名字还挺醒目的。
Thanks to a little something called Helvetica Bold 24-point.
这多亏有了24针Helvetic打印机。
Man, we're gonna rock that Asian Student Union.
哥们儿，我们要在"亚学联"盖了。
-Hey, guys. -Hey, Missy.
-嘿，伙计们。 -嘿，米西。
-Our band is playing on Friday. -Yeah, you should come check us out.
-你知道吗，我们乐队星期五演出。 -是啊，你该来看看。
We're called Way/No Way.
我们管它叫"行，还是不行"。
-No way. -Way.
-不行。 -行!
-Great. I'll be there. -Fresh.
-好吧，到时见 -新鲜
-Boss. -Mint.
-老板. -薄荷.
-She's gone. -I know it.
-她走了。 -我知道。
-I am totally gonna ask her out. -Dude, I was gonna ask her out.
-你知道吗，我一定要约到她。 -哥们儿，我还想约她呢。
-I said it first, bro. -Well, I thought it first, Homes.
-是我先说的，兄弟。 -那我还先想到的呢，老哥。
-Look, if you date.. -Wait! Wait! What are we doing?
-听着，你要是约… -等等，我们在干吗呢？
What we have is too important to mess it up over some girl.
我们俩可不能重色轻友反目成仇
I mean, we can get laid any time we want.
再说，天涯何处无芳草。
Totally.
就是。
-I had sex in high school. -Me too. I'm good at it.
-我高中就有性生活了。 -我也是，我是情场高手。
All right, I say we make a pact.
好吧，我们俩立个君子协定，
Neither of us will go out with Missy Goldberg.
谁都不许跟米西.戈尔伯格约会。
You got it.
一言为定。
That's Missy Goldberg, Phoebe Cates and Molly Ringwald..
那么，现在我们就不能跟米西.戈尔伯格 菲比.凯特
-who we can't go out with. -Those are the pacts.
-还有莫莉.里沃特约会了 -没错，约法三章。
And Sheena Easton. But we probably couldn't get her anyway.
哦，还有西娜.伊斯特 反正我们也追不上她。
Maybe not you.
你追不上她倒是真的。
Well, I officially give you permission to break the pact.
好吧，我正式授权允许你打破君子协定。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Here I go. Hey, remember how scary it used to be going up to girls in college?
好，我要上啦。 嘿，还记得上学时你跟女孩说话都慌神吗？
-Your hands are shaking. -I know. And I can't stop sweating.
-你的手在发抖呢。 -我知道，我还一个劲地冒汗。
Five, four, three. Applause.
5，4，3，鼓掌。
Yeah!
哦!
Welcome. It is Soap Opera Week here on Pyramid.
欢迎大家，这里是智力金字塔，肥皂剧之周。
Let's meet our contestants. First, Gene Lester is a database specialist.
来看看选手们 首先，是数据库专家金.拉斯特。
He's gonna be playing with Days of Our Lives star Joey Tribbiani.
他的搭档是“我们的日子” 剧中的明星 乔伊-崔比阿尼
And over here, we have Henrietta Cherry.
这位是Henrietta Cherry.
I know it can be intimidating for regular people to be around celebrities..
嘿，我知道普通人跟名人在一起时都会紧张。
but relax. I'm just like you, only better-looking and richer.
不过没事儿，我跟你差不多 就是好看点儿，钱多点儿。
She'll be playing with star of General Hospital, Leslie Charleson.
…她要跟"综合医院" 剧中的明星莱丝莉.查尔森搭档。
Welcome, everybody. Good luck to all of you. Let's play Pyramid.
欢迎大家，祝各位好运。 我们开始玩智力金字塔，好吗？
All right? Now, we flipped a coin before the show.
我们在节目开始之前已经抛过硬币了。
Gene, you won the toss, so you'll start. Which category?
金，你猜对硬币，所以你先开始。
-"You Crossed the Line." -"You Crossed the Line." Joey..
-你选那组题目？ -我选"You Cross The Line"。
describe for Gene these things that have lines.
乔伊，你给金描述那些有线条的东西。
Give me 20 seconds on the clock, please. Ready? Go.
限时20秒。 预备，开始。
Okay, it's a store like a supermarket.
呃，象超市一样的商店…哦！
I see what I did there. Okay, okay. I'm writing in my..
我明白，我明白。 呃，我写…
-Diary. -No, more like a notebook.
-日记。 -不是，更象个笔记本…该死！
If I'm building a house, the plan..
哦，要是我建所房子
isn't called a "shmooprint"..
那个规划，不是叫平面图的…
I can't do that either?
带个图字都不行？
In high school, I once had sex with a girl right in the middle of the..?
在高中，有一次我跟个女孩在…
-Cafeteria? -Yeah, but they're not looking for that.
-校食堂。 -是有过那么一次，但那不是他们要的那个词
-Thank you so much for this. -You like it?
-你们办的还真不错。 -哦，你喜欢吗？
Oh, my God, it's all so elegant.
哦，我的上帝，还挺高雅的呢。
When's the dirty stuff starting?
什么时候开始来点儿刺激的？
-What? -The strippers and the guys dancing..
-什么？ -你知道的，脱衣舞男啦
and, you know, pee-pees flying about.
男子艳舞啦，PP晃来晃去之类的。
Phoebe, I.. There isn't gonna be any "flying about."
菲比，我… 今天没有艳舞表演。
We thought we were a little too mature for stuff like that.
事实上，我们觉得我们老大不小的了 还玩这些？
Oh, okay.
哦，好吧。
I see what you're doing. That's fine. This is all there is. Just tea. Okay.
我知道你们在干吗，好的。 今天就是个茶话会，好的。
Raunchy.
呒，真脏啊。
Seriously, Phoebe, it's not gonna be that kind of a party.
真的，菲比，这不是那种狂欢。
Really? So this is..?
真的？这就是
This is my big sendoff into married life?
我的婚前单身告别会？
Rachel, this is the only bachelorette party I'm ever gonna have.
瑞秋，我可就只有这一次单身告别会啊。
I've got a big wad of ones in my purse.
我提包里可有一大筐的酒呢。
Really? I mean, really? It's just tea?
真的？今天就只是茶话会？
No.
当然不是了。
-Phoebe, of course there's more. -Okay.
-菲比，还有别的呢。 -好吧
I mean, let me just go talk to Monica..
我是说，我去问问莫妮卡
and get an ETA on the pee-pees.
看什么时候上PP艳舞。
We've got a problem.
我们有点问题
Oh, my God. Did someone find my Band-Aid in their scone?
哦, 天啊! 有谁发现我的橡皮膏在他们的烤饼里了吗?
That wasn't an apricot?
那不是一个杏仁吗?
-What's the problem? -Okay. Phoebe wants a stripper.
-什么问题? 菲比想要脱衣舞男
I thought we said we were too grown up for that.
我记得我说过 我们长大了, 不需要那个了
Yeah, well, it's what she wants.
对, 但是她想要的
Hey, why is the page that has strippers on it dog-eared?
嘿, 为什么有脱衣舞男电话的一页折上了?
Chandler was in Tulsa. I was bored.
钱德在Tulsa. 我太无聊了
Please don't tell him.
请别告诉他
Now, Gene, I must remind you, you need all six of these to stay in the game.
现在, 金, 我要提醒你 必须答对全部6题才能留下来
Describe for Joey "things you find in your refrigerator."
给乔伊描述冰箱里的物品。
They might as well just give us the points.
我看这简直是给我们送分啊。
Give me 20 seconds on the clock. Ready? Go.
限时20秒。预备，开始。
-You put this in your coffee. -A spoon. Your hands. Your face.
-你往咖啡里加的东西。 -勺子，手，脸。
-It's white. -Paper. Snow. A ghost!
-它是白色的。 -纸，雪，鬼！
-It's heavier than milk. -A rock. A dog. The Earth.
-它比牛奶重。 -呃，石头，狗，地球。
Pass.
过。
-You put it on a sandwich. -Salami. Anchovies. Jam.
-你往三明治上放的东西。 -萨拉米香肠，凤尾鱼，果酱。
-It's white. -Paper. Snow. A ghost!
-白色的。 -纸，雪，鬼！
-It's made from eggs. -Chickens?
-它使用鸡蛋做的。 -小鸡？
Pass.
过
-You put this on a hamburger. -Ketchup! Relish!
-你往汉堡包上放的东西。 -番茄酱。
Stop!
停。
Oh, time's up. Well, Joey, you were..
哦，时间到。 乔伊，你…
almost on a roll there. Gene..
差点儿就上榜了。金..
you'll have a chance to go to the Winner's Circle, but now..
你下半场还可能有机会进入决胜圈的。 但是现在...
Henrietta, you're going to the Winner's Circle to try your luck for $10,000..
亨瑞达 你待会儿将进入决胜圈一试运气赢取$10000。
right after this. Don't go away.
不要走开。
And we're out.
我们出局了
-How about that ketchup thing, huh? -Yeah. Impressive.
-刚才的番茄酱怎么样啊? -对!印象深刻
Oh, so we didn't win. But it's fun to play the game, right?
哦，我们没赢，不过乐在其中也不错，对吧？
I got a kid starting college. I have to get surgery on my knee.
我有个孩子刚上大学，我的膝盖要做手术
You just lost me 10 grand.
你刚刚让我损失一万美金。
Oh, wow.
喔。
I'm so sorry. Okay, I promise, we'll do better next time.
抱歉，我保证下一轮我们发挥好一点。
Well, I will, because I won't be playing with you.
我会发挥好一些，因为我不会跟你搭档了。
Hey, some of those are pretty hard.
你要知道，有些题目也太难了点。
Like, why would there be a ghost in my fridge?
例如我的冰箱里怎么会有鬼的？
Yeah.
是啊
-So Saturday night? -I'd love to.
-那么，星期六晚上。 -我很愿意。
Great.
太好了。
So how come it took you so long to ask me out?
你怎么这么长时间才约我？
Oh, well, this is gonna sound kind of silly..
呃，这听起来有些愚蠢，但是…
but do you remember my roommate, Chandler Bing?
你还记得我的室友 钱德-宾？
Sure. He was in your "band."
当然，他在你的"乐队"里。
It's been 16 years, but the air quotes still hurt.
已经16年了，不过那个引号还是挺伤人的。
-Sorry. -That's okay. Anyway..
-对不起。 -没关系。
Well, he and I both really liked you a lot..
呃，总之，我们那时都很喜欢你，
but we didn't want it to jeopardize our friendship, so we made a pact..
但是我们又不想为此伤友谊 所以我们约定
that neither of us could ask you out.
谁也不能跟你约会。
-Really? -Yeah, why?
-真的？ -是啊，怎么了？
Well, Chandler and I used to make out.
呃，钱德和我经常一块儿亲热。
A lot.
经常
-You did? -Yeah.
-你们俩？ -对呀
-We'd go to the science lab after-hours. -And on my turf?!
-我们常在下课后到实验室去。 -还在我的地盘上？
Hey, where is this guy? It's been over an hour.
嘿，那家伙还没来？都一个多小时了。
He's coming from Jersey. He said he'd get here as fast as he could.
他要从Jersey赶过来，他说会尽快赶到的。
Oh, by the way, Phoebe's friend Marge found an earring in cucumber sandwich.
哦, 对了, 菲比的朋友马切 在黄瓜三文治中发现了一只耳环
Well, it's not mi..
呃.........它不是我的..
I am not on my game today.
我今天没有玩游戏
-Who is it? -It's the police.
-谁呀？ -警察。
The police!
哦，警察！
That's right. It's Officer Goodbody.
没错，是"好身材"警官。
What's the matter, officer? Has someone been bad?
出什么事啦，警官？是不是有人调皮了？
That's a lot of stairs.
唔，这么多楼梯。
Boy.
唔，老天！
You should warn people there's no elevator.
你们应该告诉人家这栋楼没电梯。
I should not have had that Mexican food for lunch.
我午饭不该吃墨西哥菜。
Are you gonna be okay, Officer..?
你没事吧，警官…
-Goodbody. -If you say so.
-"好身材" -你非要那么说的话。
So where's the young lady..
那么，哪位是
who I am supposed to take downtown?
我要“逮捕”的年轻女士啊？
Oh, God.
哦，上帝。
You, my dear, are under arrest.
你, 亲爱的, 被捕啦!!!(不许动)
Cardiac arrest?
心博停止了?
All right. Somebody show me where to plug in my box..
好了，谁告诉我插座在哪
and we'll get this party started.
我们开始狂欢吧。
-Over here? -Yeah.
-在这? -对啊!
-All right. -Rachel?
-好吧 -瑞秋？
-Yeah? -Are you kidding?
-啊？ -呃，你是不是在开我的玩笑？
We didn't know you wanted a stripper, so we got the phone book..
好吧，我们原来不知道你想要脱衣舞男 所以...
-and got the first name we could find. -How old's your phone book?
-我们临时在电话簿上找了一个。 -你们的电话簿有多老了？
Oh, my God, this man is gonna get naked in my apartment.
哦，我的上帝 这个男人要在我的公寓里脱光光！
God, no. I don't wanna see him take his clothes off.
哦，上帝，不要。我可不想看他跳脱衣舞。
Are you talking about me?
你们在说我吗？
No.
哦，不。
I mean, obviously we wanna see you take your clothes off.
我是说，我们显然是要看你跳脱衣舞的，
You big piece of eye candy.
你这个万人迷。
Okay. Okay, ladies, can I have your attention, please?
好的，女士们，请注意了。
Oh, yeah.
哦！！
Did someone call for the long arm of the law?
有人呼唤法律的巨擘了吗？
I should warn you, I have a concealed weapon.
我要警告你，我有秘密武器呦。
I hope you're familiar with this state's penal code.
我希望你们熟悉本州法律规则。
Okay, okay. Enough teasing.
好了好了，玩笑开够了
Now for some pleasing.
现在该乐一乐了。
She cringed.
喔，她躲着我。
This is how I look when I'm turned-on.
这就是我兴奋时候的样子。
You were talking about me before.
你们刚才就是在说我。
Look, I don't need this. I'm out of here. Where's my hat?
我可不需要这些。 我要走了，我的帽子呢？
Look, I've been in this business for a long time.
我干这行已经很长时间了。
Shocking.
骇人听闻。
Now, if you'll just pay me my $300, I'll be on my way.
现在，你付我300块，我这就走人。
-$300? Are you kidding? -That's okay. Let me get my checkbook.
-300？你开什么玩笑？ -没关系，我来拿支票。
You're not gonna pay him. He didn't do anything.
不，你不用付他钱，他什么也没干。
Didn't do anything? I took a bus all the way from Hoboken.
什么也没干？ 我大老远的从Holbolken搭公交车赶来
I climbed, I don't know, like, a billion stairs.
我爬了，天知道的，上亿的台阶。
And it's not like I can take them two at a time.
这可不像是我平时的消遣。
I don't care. We're not paying you $300 for this.
我不管，我们才不会就为这个付给你300块钱。
It's not my fault if you're too uptight to appreciate..
那好，你那么保守 欣赏不了男性的身材和魅力
the male form in all its glory.
这又不是我的错。
Okay, I'm uptight. That's why I don't wanna watch a middle-aged guy..
哦，是，我保守，对 所以我不想看个半大老头儿...
dance around in what I can only assume is a child's Halloween costume.
穿一身 我敢说是小孩万圣节的行头跳脱衣舞。
I may have borrowed this from my nephew..
我也许是从我侄子那儿借的衣服
but let me assure you, what's underneath is all man.
但我担保衣服里头可是货真价实的真男人。
I'm sorry, did you say "all man" or "old man"?
哦，抱歉，你是说真男人还是老男人？
You're mean.
哦，你可真刻薄。
-Look, officer.. Sir? -Damn it.
-哦，瞧，警官… -哦，该死，啊！
Big surprise. The hunk of beef has feelings.
没想到吧，大胖子也很脆弱。
Applause.
鼓掌。
Okay, Henrietta, you picked "Jack and Jill Went Up The Hill."
好，亨瑞达 你选了"Jack and Jill Went Up The Hill"。
My friend Rachel has a kid. I totally know nursery rhymes.
我朋友瑞秋有个小孩，我对儿歌很熟悉。
Joey, describe these things associated with the United States Congress.
乔伊，描述以下跟美国国会有关的事物。
Give me 20 seconds on the clock, please.
限时20秒。
Ready? Go.
预备，开始。
Pass.
过
-The thing hanging in your throat. -Uvula.
-呃，你喉咙后面挂着的小东西。 -悬雍垂(小舌头)。
Then pass.
哦，那，过。
Okay. Henrietta, you didn't get all the points you needed..
好了，亨瑞达，你没有得到所需的点数
so that means, Gene, you are going to the Winner's Circle to try for $10,000.
所以，那就意味着，Gene 你将进入决胜圈来赢取$10000
And you're gonna be going there with Joey Tribbiani.
而且你将与 乔伊-崔比阿尼 一起参赛。
Pass.
过
Nope. You must be thinking of someone else.
不行, 你要为别人着想
I was never in a band.
我从来没加入过乐队
You made out with Missy Goldberg?
你跟米西.戈尔伯格亲热过？
How could you do that after you promised me?
你怎么能在向我保证过之后还这么做？
Excuse me.
失陪一下。
That didn't make us sound gay at all.
那听起来倒一点不象同性恋。
-You broke the pact. -Ross, that was 16 years ago.
-你违反了君子协定。 -罗斯，那是16年前的事了。
That doesn't matter. We're talking about the foundation of our friendship.
那也不行，现在说的是我们之间友谊的基础。
I believe the foundation of our friendship was unfortunate hair.
我以为我们之间友谊的基础是难堪的发型。
If we're really gonna do this, it's not like you never broke one of the pacts.
好吧，你看，要是我们真的明算账的话， 你也不是没干过违反君子协定的事。
-I didn't. -Oh, really?
-我没有。 -真的？
-No. -Oh, really?
-没有。 -真的？！
-No. -Adrienne Turner.
-没有。 -安卓.特娜
Yes?
在.
-Hey, Adrienne. -Hey, Adrienne. Hey.
-嘿, 安卓 -嘿, 安卓. 嘿
I never did anything with Adrienne Turner.
我从没跟安卓.特娜搅和到一起。
Oh, please. And you knew how much I liked her.
哦，得了吧，你知道我有多喜欢他。
I don't know what you're talking about.
我不知道你在说什么。
Really? Remember that party freshman year?
真的？还记得那个入学后第一个圣诞节假期 前一周的晚会吗？
A week before Christmas vacation? I do.
前一周的晚会吗？
You had some visitors.
我记得，当时有人找你。
I can't believe we're at a real college party.
难以置信我们在一个真的大学聚会上。
I have to pee so bad.
我兴奋的直想尿尿。
This is so awesome.
这可真棒。
College guys are so cute.
大学男生好可爱。
-Hey, you've got a boyfriend. -I know.
-嘿，你有男朋友了。 -我知道
But if a guy who looks like Corey Haim wants to kiss me, I am so gonna let him.
不过要是有个象克瑞.哈姆那样的想亲我 我是不会拒绝的。
Hey, look, there's Chandler.
嘿，那是钱德。
That stupid friend of Ross' who said I was fat.
你知道的，罗斯的傻朋友，说我胖的那个。
-I've already lost four pounds. -You can so totally tell.
-你要知道，我都瘦掉4磅了。 -就是，一眼就看得出来。
I know!
我就知道！
Well, let's see, maybe he knows where Ross is.
问问他罗斯在哪。
Hey, how's it going?
嘿，怎么样？
-Aren't you..? -Yeah, Rachel.
-你不是… -对，瑞秋。
And this is Ross' sister, Monica. We met at Thanksgiving.
这是罗斯的妹妹，莫妮卡。 我们感恩节见过。
Right. So how you doing?
对。那，您怎么样？
Bitchen.
更浪了。
-Hi, Monica. -Hi, Chandler.
-嗨，莫妮卡。 -嗨，钱德。
It's really nice to see you. Not!
我是说，见到你很高兴...才怪。
Okay.
好吧。
I'll see if I can find Ross.
我看看能不能找到罗斯。
Oh, my God, Rach. Beanbag chairs.
哦, 我的天，瑞秋，充气椅。
Do not let me sit in one of those. We'll be here for days.
千万别让我坐上去，不然我们就走不了了。
Listen, Adrienne, you can't tell Chandler about this.
听着，安卓，你可不能告诉钱德。
Oh, believe me, Ross, I won't be telling anybody about this.
哦，相信我，罗斯，我不会告诉任何人的。
Cool.
酷。
No way.
不可能
I didn't know you knew about that.
我以为你不知道。
Well, I did. And it hurt.
但是我知道了，我还很伤心。
That's when I wrote the song "Betrayal in the Common Room."
所以我才写了"在休息室被背叛"那首歌。
That's why that song had so much power.
所以那首歌才那么带劲
Man, I'm sorry.
嘿，对不起。
Look, that was a long time ago.
好了，那都是陈年往事了。
So I made out with Adrienne, and you made out with Missy.
那，我跟安卓亲热，而你跟米西亲热。
Well, I guess we're even.
我看我们俩扯平了。
We are even, right?
我们俩扯平了，对吧？
One more thing. I was so pissed at you that night, I wanted to get back at you.
还有一件事。 那晚我特生你的气，想报复你
So I thought, "Who does Ross like more than anybody?"
所以我当时想，谁是罗斯最喜欢的人呢。
What did you do to my mom?
你对我妈做了什么？
Not her.
不是她。
I am so drunk.
我可真醉了。
That's weird. I've had the same number of beers as you and don't feel anything.
那就怪了，我跟你喝的差不多 怎么我一点事儿没有。
So you girls having fun?
你们俩玩的好吗？
For your information, ass-munch..
跟你说，好的不得了。
I've lost four pounds. Maybe even five with all the dancing.
我瘦了4磅，没准儿跳完舞会瘦5磅。
-Somebody order a pizza? -Oh, that's me!
-有人定比萨饼了吗？ -哦，是我。
I am so not gonna do good on my SATs tomorrow.
我明天的入学考试算是没戏了。
Well, maybe you could go to school here next year and we could totally hang out.
那，明年也许你可以到我们这儿来上大学 我们可以一块玩玩。
Oh, yeah. There's a plan.
哦，对，你说得挺轻松，
Why don't I just start taking my smart pills now.
那我干脆现在就吃点脑灵通得了。
Well, maybe you could get in on a beauty scholarship.
唔，没准儿你能拿到选美奖学金呢。
What a line.
哦，别骗人了
-So where are you applying to? -Well..
-那，你都申请了哪些学校？ -唔..
I think it's kind of really important that I go somewhere where there's sun.
你知道，我觉着我要去的地方应该阳光明媚 这很重要，所以我想…
So I'm sort of.. Hey!
所以我想…嗨！
I'm in college, and I'm in a band.
我是大学生，还是乐队成员。
Yeah, okay.
那好吧。
What's the matter? You never saw a 50-year-old stripper cry before?
怎么啦，你们没见过五十岁的脱衣舞男哭过吗？
You know, it's fine. We'll pay you.
你看，算了吧，我们付你钱还不行吗。
No, no, you're right. Who am I kidding?
不是那么回事儿，你说的对，我在开谁的玩笑？
I should have hung up that breakaway jockstrap years ago.
早几年我就该用那条脱开的护身带上吊算了。
Half the time, it just pops off by itself.
经常的它自己就断开了
Maybe now is a good time for cake and presents.
也许现在应该是蛋糕和礼物的时间
What am I gonna do? I mean..
现在我该怎么办？
this has been my life for 32 years.
我是说，我干这个都32年了。
Taking my clothes off in front of people is all I know.
我只会在人家面前脱衣服。
No, there's got to be something else that you can do.
哦，等等，一定还有别的事你能做的。
I mean, what skills do you have?
我是说，你还有什么技术吗？
I don't know.
我不知道。
I can make my pecs dance.
我能跳肚皮舞。
I can pick up a dollar bill with my butt cheeks.
我可以用屁股蛋儿夹起1美元的钞票。
I can go to that special place inside me where I feel no shame.
我能变得毫无廉耻之心。
So maybe something in an office.
那你也许可以从政。
Or you could.. You could teach stripping.
或者你可以教人跳脱衣舞。
You know, share your gift. Pass the torch.
你知道吗？分享你的才能，发扬光大。
You know, actually, that's not a bad idea.
对呀，这主意不赖
I could do it out of my apartment. I don't think my mom would mind.
我可以在我的公寓外头干。 我想我妈不会介意的。
There you go. Okay. You think you're gonna be okay?
这下好啦，你感觉好一点了吧？
-Yeah. Yeah. -Yeah.
-对，好点了 -好
This is so weird.
世事难料啊。
You never know when it's gonna be your last dance.
你不会知道什么时候曲终人散。
And I didn't even get a chance to finish it.
而且我甚至都没能跳完最后一支舞。
Finish it.
那你把它跳完吧。
-What? -Your last dance. Do it for us.
-什么？ -你的最后一次，给我们跳完吧。
-Really? -Really?
-你当真？ -你当真？
Yeah. Yeah, he deserves to do the thing he loves one last time.
是的，他应该最后再做一次他喜爱的事。
Okay. All right. Get ready, ladies.
好的，准备好了，女士们。
Okay.
好了
Oh, this is so hot!
哦，这可真让人兴奋！
Oh, no, don't stop.
哦，别，别停下来。
Have to.
跳不动了。
I am so sorry that you have to do this with me.
真抱歉你要和我一起干这个
Listen, I know this won't put your kid through college..
听着, 我知道这个不能送你的孩子去大学..
but would you like a Days of our Lives mug?
但是, 你喜欢《Days of our Lives》的杯子吗
We're back in five, four, three, two..
我们现在倒数5,4,3,2..
Applause.
鼓掌
Welcome to the Winner's Circle. Joey, Gene, you guys ready?
欢迎来到决胜圈。 乔伊，金，你们准备好了吗？
-Yeah. -Sure.
-好了。 -当然。
Okay. Give me 60 seconds on the clock, please.
好，限时60秒。
Ready? Go.
预备，开始。
Oak. Maple. Elm. Birch.
橡树，枫树，榆树，桦树…
I don't know. Types of trees..?
我-我-我不知道，树种？
Buenos dias. Enchilada. Por favor.
(西班牙语)
Oh, I'm so sorry, I don't know any Spanish words.
哦，抱歉，我一点不懂西班牙语。
A match. A candle.
火柴，蜡烛…
Things that go: when you put them out.
扑灭时发出""声的东西。
A torch. A bonfire.
火炬，篝火…
-Your pee. -Things that burn.
-哦，你的小便。 -燃烧物。
"I'd like to go for a walk." "Scratch my belly."
我要去散散步。 挠挠我的肚皮。
Dude. Dude, I think you're losing it.
哥们儿，我觉得你说的太乱了。
"I have fur." "I like to bark."
呃，我有毛，我会吠叫。
What a dog says.
哦，这狗说的好啊
-Pepperoni. -Pizza toppings!
-意大利辣香肠… -比萨饼料。下一个！
Cindy Crawford. Christie Brinkley. Heidi Klum.
辛迪.克劳馥，克莉斯蒂.布林克利 海蒂.克劳姆，克劳迪娅.西佛。
Claudia Schiffer. Christy Turlington. Kate Moss.
克莉斯蒂.特林顿，凯特.玛斯…
Girls Chandler could never get?
钱德永远追不上的姑娘。
-Supermodels. -Where?
-超级名模！ -哪儿？！
I can't believe you're so upset.
真没想到你这么生气
What do you mean? You kissed Rachel.
-你说呢?你吻了瑞秋
Ross, she was so drunk she didn't even remember it the next day.
罗斯, 她喝太多了 她第二天甚至什么也不记得了
Plus, I should tell you, it did not last long.
另外我要告诉你, 那个并没持续太长
Hey!
嘿!
I'm in college, and I'm in a band.
我上大学, 而且在玩音乐
Yeah, okay.
啊, 好啊!
And now I've killed one.
而且我已经搞定了一个
Hey. Where's Rachel?
嘿，瑞秋在哪？
She and Phoebe took the stripper to the hospital.
她和菲比送脱衣舞男上医院了。
Sounds like your elegant tea party went off just as planned.
听起来好象你的"一流茶会"按计划进行
Did you know Chandler kissed Rachel?
你知不知道钱德吻过瑞秋？
What? When was this?
什么？什么时候？
Last week. We had some wine and..
上周, 我们喝了些酒, 然后..
You don't know I'm kidding.
你不知道我是开玩笑的
1987.
1987年。
The weekend you guys visited me at school.
你们俩上学校找我去的那个周末。
-Oh, my God. That's wild. -But it was, like, a million years ago.
-我的天，那也太放肆了。 -是，不过那是很久以前的事了
-It doesn't matter. -It matters to me.
-没什么要紧的。 -但那对我很要紧。
-Why? -Because the night you kissed Rachel..
-为什么？ -因为你吻瑞秋的那晚
was the night I kissed Rachel for the very first time.
是我第一次吻瑞秋。
-You kissed her that night too? -Two guys in one night?
-你那晚也吻瑞秋了？ -一晚上两个男人？
Oh, I thought she became a slut after she got her nose fixed.
我还以为她整过鼻子以后才变得放荡了呢。
-Seriously, where did this happen? -Okay..
-真的，你在哪儿吻的瑞秋？ -是这样的
after you told me she was passed out in our room..
你告诉我瑞秋在我们屋里睡了之后
I went in there to make sure she was all right.
我进去看看她怎么样了。
She was lying on my bed, all buried in people's coats.
她躺在我床上，睡在一堆衣服下面。
I went to kiss her on the forehead..
呃，我过去想吻她的额头
but it was so dark, I accidentally got her lips.
但屋里太暗，我不小心亲到了她的嘴唇
I started to pull away, but then I felt her start to kiss me back.
我想回身但我觉得她也开始吻我。
It was only for a second, but it was amazing.
那只有一瞬间但感觉太奇妙了。
And now I find out that you kissed her first.
但是现在，我却发现你先吻了她。
-Wait, what bed did you say she was on? -Mine.
-呃，等等，你刚才说她在哪张床上？ -我床上。
-I'm sure I put her on my bed. -No, she was definitely on my bed.
-我记得很清楚我把她放到我床上的。 -不对，她肯定是在我床上。
Why would I kiss a girl and then put her on your bed?
我干吗吻完一个姑娘后把她放到你床上？
Well, then who was on my bed?
那当时我床上的是谁？
No! No!
哦，哦，哦！不！不！
Yes!
是的！
-You were under the pile of coats? -I was the pile of coats!
-你在那堆衣服下面？ -那堆衣服就是我。
Oh, my God!
哦，我的上帝！
You were my midnight mystery kisser?!
你是我的午夜神秘接吻人？
You were my first kiss with Rachel?!
你是我和瑞秋的初吻？
You were my first kiss ever?!
你就是我这辈子的初吻？！
What did I marry into?!
瞧瞧我结的什么亲家。
Crap!
哦，倒霉！